<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Just a dev blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.bswiecki.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Just a dev blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.bswiecki.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>K-DAG University</title>
      <link>https://blog.bswiecki.dev/post/2019-07-14-k-dag-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.bswiecki.dev/post/2019-07-14-k-dag-university/</guid>
      <description>Last time I brefly described the knowledge in the form of a Graph structure. Each term having set of prerequisites is a node in this graph, each dependency is a directed edge in such graph.
Now let&amp;rsquo;s assume this graph is a directed acyclic one and there are no terms which form a cycle of dependencies. In reality I don&amp;rsquo;t believe this to be true but it does simplify reasoning and can definitely be achieved locally for larger terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge DAG</title>
      <link>https://blog.bswiecki.dev/post/2019-07-10-knowledge-dag/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.bswiecki.dev/post/2019-07-10-knowledge-dag/</guid>
      <description>If I have some specific problem to solve, I find technology that seems relevant, then I scan the Internet for some basic introduction, then some tutorial, then documentation.
My usual problem is that the issue I want to solve is usually not in the introduction nor the tutorial. I rarely find ready-to-use solution and unfortunately I tend to really dislike adjusting my idea to what you can easily achieve with tutorial-like solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boot</title>
      <link>https://blog.bswiecki.dev/post/2019-07-06-booting-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.bswiecki.dev/post/2019-07-06-booting-up/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, one of the hardest things - materialize your thoughts.
We&amp;rsquo;re living in a world full of digital content. People write, produce, record, put so many things into the Internet that it&amp;rsquo;s very easy to just get lost in all this informational chaos. Will this blog share the same fate? Most likely, not going to lie here.
Honestly I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if the information I could throw into the big information highway will be that meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About this blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.bswiecki.dev/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.bswiecki.dev/page/about/</guid>
      <description>This space is mostly a brain dump. I have few ideas I&amp;rsquo;d like to expore so why not do it in public.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>